HAROON BADSHAH

Full Stack Developer

Email: larvaweb999@gmail.com

Contact: 056 142 0597



CAREER OBJECTIVE

Looking for a challenging career that demands the best of my professional ability in terms of, technical and analytical skills, and helps me in broadening and enhancing my current skill and knowledge.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hardworking software development professional driven to increase team effectiveness. Focused on usability and performance improvements. Proven history of developing useful, efficient and cost-effective projects.

Software Developer skilled at technical leadership, communication and presentations. Experienced in full project life cycle from design to implementation to integration.

SKILLS

- .Net
- .Net Core
- C#.Net
- Asp.Net
- PHP
- React.is
- Web API
- Laravel
- Vue.js
- Web Hosting

- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- Power BI
- Ajax
- LiveWire
- Entity Framework
- Node Js
- SQL Server
- Strapi

- Design Patterns
- WordPress
- HTML5
- CSS
- MySQL
- JSON
- Scripting
- Project Management
- Cpanel
- MS Office

WORK HISTORY

Aug 2020 – June 2021 Web Developer

Red Stonez Peshawar

- System Architecture Designing.
- Development of a new System.
- Maintaining Existing System.
- Involving coding, Unit Testing, and database creation
- Implementing System.
- System Maintenance and Support.
- Reporting
- Graphic Designing

Environment / Technology

Laravel, PHP, Web API, Payment Gateways, WordPress, Entity Framework, MySQL, JQuery, JavaScript, Ajax, HTML, CSS

June 2021 - Dec 2022 Sr. Developer

Seven Koncepts Rawalpindi Pakistan

- Communication with Business Entities.
- Project Management
- Development of a new System.
- Involving coding, Unit Testing, and database creation.
- Implementing System.
- System Maintenance and Support.
- Reporting
- Architecture Designing,
- Web Hosting
- UI Design

Environment / Technology

Laravel, PHP, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Web API, Payment Gateways, WordPress, Entity Framework, MySQL, JQuery, JavaScript, SQL Server, .NET, Ajax, ASP, C#, Web API, Strapi, Google API, JSON, Shopify, Woo Commerce, Freed Camp, Figma, FileZilla, Vue JS, React JS,

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023 System Developer

BLS Solutions Rawalpindi Pakistan

- Development new System.
- Involving coding, Unit Testing and database creation
- Implementing System.
- UI Design
- Web Sockets
- Hardware Functionality
- System Maintenance and Support.
- Reporting.

Environment / Technology

Laravel, PHP, Web API, Payment Gateways, WordPress, Entity Framework, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap JQuery, JavaScript, SQL Server, .NET, Ajax, ASP, C#, Web API, Strapi, Google API, JSON, Shopify, Woo Commerce, Next JS, Redis,

PROJECTS

- https://www.lb908.com/
- https://burjyaqub.com/
- https://hub.broomstickcreative.com/
- https://adscc.ae/
- https://yasclinicgroup.ae/
- https://technology-empire.co.uk/
- https://comptoir102.com/

- E-Charging System
- Automatic Locker System
- Payment Transaction System
- Payment Machine Locker System

EDUCATION

April 2018

Bachelor of Science: (Computer Science)

IBMS | Peshawar, Pakistan

Mar 2014

High School Diploma

Agricultural College | Peshawar, Pakistan

CERTIFICATIONS

• Certified Full Stack Web Developer (CSM)